ROSU IOANA

UX and UI designer

+40747818585
ioanarosu22@gmail.com
github.com/ioanarosu
linkedin.com/in/ioana-rosu-wd

PROFILE

I design and build digital products for digital experiences.

I have experience building mockups with Sketch / Photoshop and implementing HTML/CSS with latest CSS3 and HTML5 features.

Some of my **public work** can be found on github:

https://github.com/ioanarosu

SKILLS

User Experience, User Interface, Digital Design, Prototyping

Tools: Photoshop, Illustrator, Sketch, InVision, Figma, Draw.io

Experienced with: HTML5, CSS3, Gulp

Concept & Practices: sketching, wireframes, responsive design, mobile

first, personas, user flow, user centered design, design thinking.

EXPERIENCE

July 2019 - September 2019

Intern UX/ UI designer Endava Iasi

In this internship program I improved my visual design skills and I became more aware of homan centered design and design thinking approach.

I worked in a team (2 members) at two projects. We designed an android app for a coffee shop and a desktop application (feedback dashboard). We started our projects, based on requirements, with user flows, continued with wireframes and built the high fidelity prototypes.

http://bit.ly/feedback-app-portfolio

http://bit.ly/coffee-shop-app

September 2017 - January 2018

UX/UI designer

Skills for Sale (https://ioanarosu.github.io/skills-for-sale/)

The idea of this project was to create an application where you can find a skilled person to solve you a specific problem.

I created personas, user flows, low-fidelity and high-fidelity wireframes and I used latest CSS techniques like Css Grid, BEM, Sass for html/css implementation.

January 2016 - December 2017 (2 years)

Part-time UX/ UI designer

Best Steak Restaurant (beststeakrestaurant.com)

I worked in a team that designed and implemented https:// www.beststeakrestaurant.com/ website. My role was to design and build the home page and do all the changes that customer required in the other pages. I built mockups with Sketch and I did also the html/css implementation. I used SASS and BEM for css generation. January 2015 - April 2017 (2 years 4 months)

Web designer

Zuppler (zuppler.com)

Zuppler.com is the complete order platform servicing restaurants, caterers, sports stadiums, hospitals, hotels, delivery services.

My activities involved:

- Design new restaurant websites, implement it in CSS and HTML with sass and gulp.
- Integrate zuppler online order online menu inside restaurant website
- Style with css3 the zuppler menu to look like the restaurant website
- Design google ads banners in Sketch
- Design cover photos for facebook
- Discuss with clients about their websites and steps to integrate with Zuppler.com

November 2014 - December 2014 (2 months)

Web designer

Delicious Doughnuts (delicious doughnuts.ro)

I created low-fidelity and high-fidelity wireframes in Sketch and html/css implementation. In this project I used foundation (grid, hamburg menu) and Sass for css generation.

EDUCATION

Interaction Design Foundation (online course)

UI and UX design. (November 2018 - present)

Romanian Interaction Lab (Iasi, Romania)

UX design · (November 2018)

Funny PC World (Iasi, Romania)

Web design · (2013 - 2015)

University (Iasi, Romania)

Bachelor's Degree, Biology/Biological Sciences, General ·

(2002 - 2006)